MARINA SAMPROVALAKI

MACHINE LEARNING ENGINEER

CONTACT

+306980884422

marina.samb14@gmail.com

linkedin.com/in/marina-samprovalaki/

github.com/marina-sam14

tinyurl.com/3ymvdp5t

Athens, Greece

EDUCATION

M.Sc. by Research, Computer Science

Athens University of Economics and Business

2023-2024

B.Sc. in Informatics

Athens University of Economics and Business

2018-2022

LANGUAGES

English

PROFILE

I am currently pursuing an MSc in Computer Science, driven by a passion for exploring diverse areas of the field. My research focuses on advancing state-of-the-art Multimodal Large Language models in the medical domain, particularly in the area of medical image captioning.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Researcher

Athens University of Economics and Business

10/2023 - today

• Researching Diagnostic Captioning with a focus on developing Multimodal Large Language Models to address the challenge of generating accurate and informative consults for medical images.

Junior Full Stack Engineer

HOMI Greece

11/2022 - 07/2023

- Data Modeling: Specialize in developing data models for predictive analytics and machine learning tasks.
- · Cloud Platform Experience: Proficient in AWS for data storage and analysis..
- Frontend Frameworks: Experienced with React
- Dataase Technologies: Skilled with MongoDB and PostgreSQL.
- Web Application Development: Experienced in modern programming languages and frameworks, adept at making API calls.

Software Engineer Intern

71 International

03/22 - 09/22

· Assisting in software development tasks, gaining hands-on experience in coding, debugging, and testing.